

Contact









Skills

- .Net (VB.net, VBA, C#)
- JavaScript/jQuery
- PHP (CodeIgniter)
- HTML/CSS/SASS
- Java
- SQL (Oracle, MySQL, MS SQL)
- Photo, Video, Audio Editing

Reference

- SOLEM KHAN ABDUSALAM
 CRM .NET Developer Techosystems +639153512601
- JICK TEZADO
 Junior Developer Codexus Solution Inc. +639058414436
- JOMAR CAGADO
 Technology Support Engr Fujitsu Cebu +639051355990



JAN MARK LAURON

Software Developer

With 4+ years of experience in software development. Specializing in developing and designing Windows, web, and mobile applications, as well as having experience with operation and maintenance support. And an ability to adapt to new technologies and challenges.



EDUCATION

2012 - 2019

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY AMA Computer Learning Center College General Santos City



WORK EXPERIENCE

July 2022 - Present

APPLICATION SYSTEMS ENGINEER

WeServ Systems International, Inc (Fujitsu PH) Cebu City

• Assigned as Layer 2 and 3 Resolver in multiple Operation and Maintenance projects. Responsible for supporting inquiries, failures, problems, and change responses.

June 2021 - July 2022

INHOUSE PROGRAMMER

General Tuna Corporation General Santos City

 Work as both a frontend and backend developer. Developed web-based applications using Codelgniter (PHP) and MySQL as databases.

Dec 2018 - May 2021

ASSOCIATE SOFTWARE ENGINEER

KCC Property Holdings Inc - KCC Mall of Gensan General Santos City

• Work as both a frontend and backend developer. Developed Windows applications using Vb.net and C#; web-based applications using ASP.NET/MVC; and mobile development using NativeScript (JavaScript). Developing applications using MS SQL, MariaDB, and Oracle as databases.

Apr 2017 - June 2017

LAYOUT ARTIST

A & L Rabbi Ads and Craft General Santos City

• Responsible for creating a layout design for medals, mugs, plaques, button pins, and tarpaulins.



ACHIEVEMENTS/SEMINARS

Dec 12, 2018

VISUAL GRAPHICS DESIGN NCIII

Mary Mediatrix of All Grace Academy, Inc. - Digos City

Sept 5-7, 2018

20th NATIONAL TUNA CONGRESS SM Mall of Gensan, Trade Hall 1

Sept 15-16, 2016

SOX ICT STARTUP CHALLENGE

Best in Concept/Prototype - 1st Place Veranza Mall, General Santos City